Guide to the Ann Weisgarber Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Ann Weisgarber Accessions
1989-2017
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Weisgarber, Ann
UPWC.17096
10 boxes
Multiple accessions documenting the writing career of Ann Weisgarber, author of The Personal History of Rachel Dupree (2010), The Promise (2013), and The Glovemaker (2019).
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research
Scope and Contents
Multiple accessions documenting the writing career of Ann Weisgarber, author of The Personal History of Rachel Dupree (2010), The Promise (2013), and The Glovemaker (2019).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ann Weisgarber, 2017 and 2019
Biographical Notes
Ann Weisgarber lives in Galveston, Texas and is the author of several novels. Her first, The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, is set in the South Dakota Badlands in 1917. It was nominated for England's 2009 Orange Prize and for the 2009 Orange Award for New Writers. In the United States, The Personal History of Rachel DuPree won the Stephen Turner Award for New Fiction and the Langum Prize for American Historical Fiction. JuVee Productions has optioned the film rights and Viola Davis will play Rachel DuPree. Filming is scheduled for 2018.
Weisgarber's second novel, The Promise, takes place in 1900 on Galveston Island at the time of America's deadliest natural disaster. It was shortlisted for the United Kingdom's Walter Scott Prize for Historical Fiction, was the finalist for the Spur Award for Best Western Historical Fiction, and was a finalist for the Ohioana Book Award for Fiction. Her third book to date, The Glovemaker, was published in 2018 and is set in Utah's deep canyon country during the winter of 1888.
Weisgarber's archive preserves many aspects of her writing career: her early works including poetry and short stories, interviews, manuscript drafts, research materials, correspondence with editors, agents, and readers, reviews and publicity material, foreign editions and artifacts. Also present are materials from her tenure as the artist-in-residence at Badlands National Park while she was working on The Personal History of Rachel Dupree.
Weisgarber was born and raised in Ohio and graduated from Wright State University in Dayton with a Bachelor of Arts in Social Work. She earned a Master of Arts in Sociology from the University of Houston and became a social worker in psychiatric and nursing home facilities and also taught sociology at Wharton County Junior College in Texas.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Weisgarber, Ann
- Accession 2017-096, This accession consists of archival materials relating to the writing career of author, Ann Weisgarber from 1989-2017. Majority of the materials in the collection are research and drafts for Weisgarber's various works such as The Personal History of Rachel DuPree and The Promise. The collection also includes correspondence with publishers such as Pan MacMillan; articles written by Weisgarber; and materials from writing conferences and workshops. The folder titles preceding a semicolon reflect Weisgarber's original descriptions.
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; Correspondence from Rights Assistant, Beverly Gadsden, speaking on 2 copies of The Promise in Portuguese, September 24, 2014 (Box 2636, Folder 1)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; Correspondence between Weisgarber and Pan MacMillan publishers, August 15, 2011 - September 23, 2014 (Box 2636, Folder 2)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; Correspondence with Pan MacMillan Publishers about selling The Promise to U.S. and film option, October 3, 2014 - May 15, 2017 (Box 2636, Folder 3)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; Materials and notes usedfor research for The Promise, June 6, 2011 - July 13, 2012 (Box 2636, Folder 4)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; "The Day I Can't Forget" by Louise Hopkins, undated (Box 2636, Folder 5)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan-Photo for The Promise"; Photograph used as model for description of Bernadette in The Promise, circa 1900s (Box 2636, Folder 6)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; "A New Directory for the Public Worship of God Wedding Ceremony and early drafts of The Promise, undated (Box 2636, Folder 7)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan-Early Drafts-The Promise Writing Critique Groups"; Annotated The Promise early drafts, undated (Box 2636, Folder 8)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan-French Reviews, Rachel DuPree"; French book reviews, 2010 (Box 2636, Folder 9)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan-Research Galveston The Promise"; Research on the 1900 Galveston hurricane, 2009-2010 (Box 2636, Folder 10)
  - "Research-The Promise, Email with Pan MacMillan"; Research for The Promise, 1997 (Box 2636, Folder 11)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Correspondence between Weisgarber and The Langum Charitable Trust, July 7, 2011 (Box 2636, Folder 12)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Texas Institute of Letters 2008 Awards, July 2008 - April 2009 (Box 2636, Folder 13)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Correspondence pertaining to The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, 2009-2010 (Box 2636, Folder 14)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Note that came with Advanced Reader's Copy of The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, and Pan MacMillan promotional material, 2008 (Box 2636, Folder 15)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Interview for The Guardian, editorial notes, and notes, 2007 (Box 2636, Folder 16)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Page proofs for The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, including a letter from Editor Will Atkins, pgs. 1-150 (1 of 2), February 21, 2008 (Box 2636, Folder 17)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Page proofs for The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, including a letter from Editor Will Atkins, pgs. 151-307 (2 of 2), February 21, 2008 (Box 2636, Folder 18)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Interviews, letter from Pan MacMillan, tickets for awards, April - June 2009 (Box 2636, Folder 19)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree correspondence about Orange Prize and Orange Award for New Writers, March 2009 - April 2010 (Box 2636, Folder 20)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Correspondence with Literary Agents when Rachel DuPree longlisted for Orange Prize in the U.K., August 2006 - November 2009 (Box 2636, Folder 21)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree correspondence with Texas Institute of Letters, won Best Work of First Fiction, November 2008 - May 2009 (Box 2636, Folder 22)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree manuscript submitted to Pan MacMillan in London, April 15, 2007 (Box 2636, Folder 23)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree manuscript, undated (Box 2636, Folder 24)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Photographs in the Orange Award for New Writers, and correspondence from Pan MacMillan, June 2009 - May 2011 (Box 2636, Folder 25)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; Sample cover of The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, including note to Ann about the cover from Valérie Maréchal, undated (Box 2636, Folder 26)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree Annotated galley proofs, pgs. 1-150 (1 of 2), February 11, 2008 (Box 2636, Folder 27)
  - "Rachel DuPree-MNW ARC French Edition"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree Annotated galley proofs, pgs. 151-307 (2 of 2), February 11, 2008 (Box 2636, Folder 28)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Email correspondence with Walker Scott, Rebecca Salt, and Lindsey Fraser, October 27, 2014 - March 24, 2017 (Box 2636, Folder 29)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Highland Park Literary Festival "Write Your World" Schedule of Events pamphlet and 26th Annual Southern Festival of Books booklet, February 27 - October 12, 2014 (Box 2636, Folder 30)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Hill Country Author Series flyer and bookmarker, and photocopy of Weisgarber speaking at Author Series, November 17, 2014 (Box 2636, Folder 31)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Brewin Dolphin Borders Book Festival Guest and Author badges, June 12-15, 2014 - June 11-14, 2015 (Box 2637, Folder 1)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Badges for conferences and book festivals, 2014-2015 (Box 2637, Folder 2)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; TLA Badges, 2015 (Box 2637, Folder 3)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Badges, 2004-2016 (Box 2637, Folder 4)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; Correspondence, UHV/ABR Reading Series Guest Speaker Ann Weisgarber flyer, and Girlfriend Weekend booklet, January 15, 2015 - April 18, 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 5)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences-TIL"; Texas Institute of Letters Agenda, Directory, and correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 2637, Folder 6)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences-Events The Promise"; Correspondence, articles, and presentation schedule for events Weisgarber attended, 2015-2016 (Box 2637, Folder 7)
  - "General-Conferences Workshops/Residences"; 30th Annual Summer Program ofthe Antioch Writers' Workshop schedule, Jentel Artist Residency Program info., Weisgarber's first panel program, 2008-2015 (Box 2637, Folder 8)
  - "Early Writing"; Lucidity: Journal of Verse and The Detroit Black Writer's Guild presents Best of Show, 1997-1999 (Box 2637, Folder 9)
  - "Early Writing"; The Islander magazines, March - May 2007 (Box 2637, Folder 10)
  - "Early Writing"; Four copies of The Islander magazines, Sugar Land magazine, and Mail Call Journal, Summer/Fall 1998 - Winter 2008 (Box 2637, Folder 11)
  - "Early Writing"; Letters about submissions for awards and contests, 1996-2006 (Box 2637, Folder 12)
  - "Early Writing"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree outline, website article about The Personal History… and notes, 2005-2008 (Box 2637, Folder 13)
  - "Early Writing"; Lucidity: A Quarterly Journal of Verse, Since 1985, Winter 1998 (Box 2637, Folder 14)
  - "Early Writing"; Awards, 1997-1999 (Box 2637, Folder 15)
  - "Early Writing-Manuscripts that didn't get off the ground"; Untitled manuscript and research for manuscript, 2008 (Box 2637, Folder 16)
  - "Early Writing-Pete"; Correspondence, "Pete" poem copies, and Editor's Choice Award, 1996 (Box 2637, Folder 17)
  - "Early Writing"; Poems titled "Prayer", annotated "Tourist Attraction", "Texans", and annotated "State Historical Site Rangers", undated (Box 2637, Folder 18)
  - "Early Writing"; Poems titled "Pioneer Woman", "Sod Hut on the Prairie", "Kansas", "What a Prairie Man Looks For", "The Oregon Trail", "Love Poems are Passe", and "Not Always So Smart", undated (Box 2637, Folder 19)
  - "Early Writing"; Annotated "The Old Noonan Place" poem, undated (Box 2637, Folder 20)
  - "Early Writing"; Poems titled "On Being 13", "Nights", "My Story", and "Lifeguards", undated (Box 2637, Folder 21)
  - "Early Writing"; Annotated drafts titled "As Emma Scrubs the Chamber Pot", "Beads", "Civil Defense Alert", "Whispers at the Ruins", and "Dancing with Buffaloes", 1996 (Box 2637, Folder 22)
  - "Early Writing"; Poems titled "Delicate Arch", "If Only for a Minute", "Dr. Mudd", "The Draft", and "Earliest Memory", 1997-1999 (Box 2637, Folder 23)
  - "Early Writing"; Drafts titled "Elizabeth Griscom Ross Ashburn Claypoole", "Funny Things", "Getting Ready", "It Seems I Still Miss You", and "Just Desserts", January 1997 (Box 2637, Folder 24)
  - "Early Writing"; Drafts titled "Kate Shelley's Storm", "Lifeguards", "A Message to General Washington", "The Prom", "Tell Us", and "Sorry", 1999 (Box 2637, Folder 25)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Editorial notes from Mantle and letters from Samuel to Deborah, May - July 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 26)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Emails with editors Maria Rejt, Josie Humber, copyeditor Mary Chamberlain, and agent Margaret Halton, May - July 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 27)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Feedback from writing group, undated (Box 2637, Folder 28)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated manuscript drafts, August 18, 2016 - May 26, 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 29)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapter 12 drafts, undated (Box 2637, Folder 30)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 9-12, July 30, 2016 - May 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 31)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 9, 10, 12, & 13, undated (Box 2637, Folder 32)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated drafts, January 2017 (Box 2637, Folder 33)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 13, 15-17, September 6, 2016 - December 21, 2016 (Box 2637, Folder 34)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 14, 16-17, October 30, 2016 - December 15, 2016 (Box 2637, Folder 35)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated drafts, October - November 2016 (Box 2638, Folder 1)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 16-19 drafts, September 2016 - March 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 2)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 18-19 drafts, February - June 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 3)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated chapters 18-31, September 2016 - June 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 4)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Annotated drafts of prologue and chapters 1-21, December 2016 - July 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 5)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Draft of revisions that were sent on May 28, 2017, to Josie Humber at Mantle (Pan MacMillan) (Box 2638, Folder 6)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; The Glovemaker manuscript sent to Josie Humber & Maria Ryft-Mantle, July 2, 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 7)
  - "Rachel DuPree Film Option Screenplay-Correspondence"; Film options from JuVee Productions, correspondence about Rachel DuPree and film options, and Rachel DuPree screenplay, January 2011 - December 2016 (Box 2638, Folder 8)
  - "Rachel DuPree Film Option Screenplay-Correspondence"; Annotated The Personal History of Rachel DuPree manuscripts, February 9, 2015 - April 15, 2016 (Box 2638, Folder 9)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Correspondence about Ohioana Book Award nomination and other awards, November 2013 - November 2014 (Box 2638, Folder 10)
  - "Utah Manuscripts-The Glovemaker-Early Drafts"; Correspondence with other authors such as Bren McClain, Dr. Flanagan, December 3, 2003 - January 18, 2016 (Box 2638, Folder 11)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Correspondence about The Promise and reviews, January 2004 - January 2016 (Box 2638, Folder 12)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Correspondence, June 2014 - February 2017 (Box 2638, Folder 13)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Meet and Greet flyer and Houston Chronicle article on The Promise, April 14, 2014 (Box 2638, Folder 14)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Weisgarber's The Promise book tour materials including Queen of the Waves CD, October 2015 (Box 2638, Folder 15)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Nominations for Friends In Deed Award, Western Writers of America Spur Award, including Borders Book Festival booklet, March 2014 - December 2015 (Box 2638, Folder 16)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Reviews of The Promise, August 2013 - January 2015 (Box 2638, Folder 17)
  - "The Promise-Honors"; Town & Country and Western Writers of America Finalist in Best Western Historical novel certificate, May 2014 (Box 2639, Folder 1)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Materials about the Badlands and Devil's Tower (1 of 2), 1989-2007 (Box 2639, Folder 2)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Materials bout the Badlands and Devil's Tower (2 of 2), 1989-2007 (Box 2639, Folder 3)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Rachel DuPree AW Proof comments, letters from editors, and The Promise draft, February 2008 - November 2013 (Box 2639, Folder 4)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Artist-in-Residence program in Badlands National Park, including research notes for Rachel DuPree, December 31, 1998 - June 15, 1999 (Box 2639, Folder 5)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree chapters 6-10 drafts, contains Alice McDermitt's notes, July 2003 (Box 2639, Folder 6)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree correspondence with publishers, and Will Atkins, editor at MacMillan, 2004-2007 (Box 2639, Folder 7)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Thanksgiving Found annotated drafts of chapters 1-8, undated (Box 2639, Folder 8)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Research notes for The Personal History of Rachel DuPree, undated (Box 2639, Folder 9)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Correspondence, and pictures from Badlands National Park Writing Residency, April 1999 - March 2009 (Box 2639, Folder 10)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Looking Over Jordan (original title to Rachel DuPree) Table of Contents and chapters 2-17, November 23, 2003 - September 15, 2005 (Box 2639, Folder 11)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree chapters 1-21, including the fourth ending to the novel, January 1, 2006 - April 15, 2007 (Box 2639, Folder 12)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Manuscript chapters 2-19, April 9, 2007 - April 15, 2007 (Box 2639, Folder 13)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Incomplete outline of The Earth Only Endures (a original title to Rachel DuPree), synopsis and correspondence, 2001-2007 (Box 2639, Folder 14)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Materials from Weisgarber's time at the Sewanee Writing Workshop, includes feedback on Rachel DuPree from classmates, July 2003 (Box 2639, Folder 15)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Synopsis for Junction (an original title for The Glovemaker) and notes for Utah manuscript, January 2, 2001 - September 20, 2001 (Box 2639, Folder 16)
  - "Rachel DuPree Drafts"; Weisgarber's National Park Services Volunteer name badge, undated (Box 2639, Folder 17)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; "Utah" manuscript turned in to agent, Margaret [Holter] in London, December 2016 (Box 2639, Folder 18)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Annotated manuscript draft, November 2016 (Box 2639, Folder 19)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Annotated manuscript prologue and chapter one drafts, June 2012 - October 2016 (Box 2639, Folder 20)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Junction annotated drafts, October 2012 - December 2016 (Box 2639, Folder 21)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Annotated drafts, 2014-2016 (Box 2639, Folder 22)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Junction chapter 4 drafts, May 2013 - December 2016 (Box 2639, Folder 23)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Junction annotated manuscript drafts, November 2016 - June 2017 (Box 2639, Folder 24)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Junction annotated chapters 7-9 drafts, June 14, 2016 - May 26, 2017 (Box 2640, Folder 1)
  - "Utah Manuscript Drafts"; Annotated chapters 8, 10, & 11, July 18, 2016 - January 18, 2017 (Box 2640, Folder 2)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Typed interviews with Texas Monthly, Viking Book Club, BookInfo.com, and bloggers, undated (Box 2640, Folder 3)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with John Siciliano, Cormac McCarthy, and Charles Frazier, 2009 (Box 2640, Folder 4)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with editor John Siciliano, Langan Kingsley, and Kristen Scharold, 2009-2015 (Box 2640, Folder 5)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with John Siciliano including "Beads" manuscript drafts, 2009-2010 (Box 2640, Folder 6)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with Vikings editor, John Siciliano and Viking publicists, March 5 - June 2, 2010 (Box 2640, Folder 7)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree Viking-U.S. Edition info. for publicity and correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 2640, Folder 8)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with John Siciliano, Langan Kingsley, Sonya Cheuse, and Maureen Donnelly, July 26, 2011 - September 16, 2013 (Box 2640, Folder 9)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with John Siciliano, October 11, 2013 - March 15, 2017 (Box 2640, Folder 10)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; The Personal History of Rachel DuPree manuscript galley proof, October 13, 2009 (Box 2640, Folder 11)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with Kristen Scharold and The Personal History of Rachel DuPree author galley, pgs. 1-180 (1 of 2), November 10-12, 2009 (Box 2640, Folder 12)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Correspondence with Kristen Scharold and The Personal History of Rachel DuPree author galley, pgs. 181-324 (2 of 2), November 10-12, 2009 (Box 2640, Folder 13)
  - "Rachel DuPree-Viking Ed.-Correspondence-Galleys"; Kristen Scharold's notes and galley proof with annotations, November 15, 2009 (Box 2640, Folder 14)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; Inserts from books such as notes from Sophie from Pan MacMillan and photographs that inspired The Promise, June 17, 2015 (Box 2640, Folder 15)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; Interview questions, early draft of The Promise, editorial comments, copy edits, prologue draft, September 13, 2012 - January 21, 2013 (Box 2640, Folder 16)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; The Promise annotated early drafts of chapters 1-14, undated (Box 2640, Folder 17)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; Annotated The Promise chapters 1-3, 5-6, 9-14, undated (Box 2640, Folder 18)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; Annotated The Promise, corrections by Weisgarber's husband, chapters 1-16 (1 of 2), January 29, 2012 (Box 2641, Folder 1)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; Annotated The Promise, corrections by Weisgarber's husband, chapters 1-16 (2 of 2), January 29, 2012 (Box 2641, Folder 2)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; The Promise includes corrections before the copy edits with Mary [Chamberlain] in England, pgs. 1-140, undated (1 of 2) (Box 2641, Folder 3)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; The Promise includes corrections before the copy edits with Mary [Chamberlain] in England, pgs. 141-311, undated (2 of 2) (Box 2641, Folder 4)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; The Promise galleys with Rob's proof comments, pgs. 1-170 (1 of 2), March 9, 2012 (Box 2641, Folder 5)
  - "The Promise-Early Drafts-Mantle Proofs-Galley Proofs"; The Promise galleys with Rob's proof comments, pgs. 171-312 (2 of 2), March 9, 2012 (Box 2641, Folder 6)
  - "The Promise-Skyhorse"; Correspondence with U.S. editor w/Skyhorse Publishing, June 8 - October 29, 2013 (Box 2641, Folder 7)
  - "The Promise-Skyhorse"; Correspondence with Skyhorse Publishing, October 30, 2013 - April 23, 2014 (Box 2641, Folder 8)
  - "The Promise-Skyhorse"; Correspondence with Skyhorse Publishing, April 28, 2014 - February 5, 2015 (Box 2641, Folder 9)
  - "The Promise-Skyhorse"; Correspondence with Skyhorse Publishing, March 2, 2015 - April 30, 2015 (Box 2641, Folder 10)
  - "The Promise-Skyhorse"; Correspondence with Skyhorse Publishing, May 4, 2015 - May 22, 2017 (Box 2641, Folder 11)